var data = {
    question1: {
        question: "Who is covered by Medi-Cal?",
        choice1: "The disabled",
        choice2: "Children in poverty",
        choice3: "Seniors between 55 and 64 years old",
        choice4: "All of the above",
        answer: "4",
        answernote: "Medi-Cal covers seniors not yet eligible for Medicare, children, and the disabled."
    },
    question2: {
        question: "The majority of Medi-Cal beneficiaries are:",
        choice1: "Adults",
        choice2: "Children",
        choice3: "The elderly",
        choice4: "The disabled",
        answer: "2",
        answernote: "The majority of Medi-Cal beneficiaries are children (54%). Seniors are 12% of beneficiaries. The disabled are 12% of beneficiaries."
    },
    question3: {
        question: "Are most Medi-Cal beneficiaries male or female?",
        choice1: "Male",
        choice2: "Female",
        answer: "2",
        answernote: "56% of Medi-Cal beneficiaries are female."
    },
    question4: {
        question: "How many California children get health coverage through Medi-Cal?",
        choice1: "One in ten",
        choice2: "One in two",
        choice3: "One in five",
        answer: "2",
        answernote: "One in two California children is covered through Medi-Cal."
    },
    question5: {
        question: "How many Californians live in an area with a shortage of primary care doctors?",
        choice1: "18 million",
        choice2: "11 million",
        choice3: "5 million",
        answer: "1",
        answernote: "Almost 18 million Californians live in an area with a shortage of primary care doctors."
    },
    question6: {
        question: "How easy is it for a Medi-Cal patient to get a doctor’s appointment, compared to someone on private health insurance?",
        choice1: "Easier",
        choice2: "About the same",
        choice3: "Harder",
        answer: "3",
        answernote: "Adults on Medi-Cal are twice as likely to have difficulties getting a doctor’s appointment, compared to adults with private insurance. This leads many Medi-Cal patients to rely on Emergency Rooms for treatment."
    },
    question7: {
        question: "California doctors lose $_____ per year because Medi-Cal is not fully funded.",
        choice1: "$1 billion",
        choice2: "$5 billion",
        choice3: "$5 million",
        answer: "2",
        answernote: "Because Medi-Cal payment rates are so low, doctors in California lose $5.2 billion every year due to Medi-Cal underfunding."
    },
    question8: {
        question: "Medi-Cal pays healthcare providers _____ the cost of providing care.",
        choice1: "100%",
        choice2: "75%",
        choice3: "50%",
        answer: "3",
        answernote: "On average, Medi-Cal pays healthcare providers like doctors and hospitals only 50% of the cost of the care they provide to Medi-Cal patients. This underfunding makes healthcare providers unwilling to accept Medi-Cal patients."
    },
    question9: {
        question: "Some primary care providers are paid only $___ for a visit with a Medi-Cal patient.",
        choice1: "$12",
        choice2: "$25",
        choice3: "$50",
        answer: "1",
        answernote: "Providers can be paid as little as $12 for a visit with a Medi-Cal patient. That’s less than the cost of a large pizza!"
    },
    question10: {
        question: "How much of care for nursing home residents is covered by Medi-Cal?",
        choice1: "1/3",
        choice2: "1/2",
        choice3: "2/3",
        answer: "3",
        answernote: "Two-thirds of nursing home residents’ care is covered by Medi-Cal."
    },
    question11: {
        question: "California hospitals receive _____ of their net funding from Medi-Cal.",
        choice1: "40%",
        choice2: "20%",
        choice3: "10%",
        answer: "2",
        answernote: "Hospitals rely on Medi-Cal for 20% of their annual net funding."
    }
};
